千機變II - 花都大戰
Twins Effect 2 : The Blade of the Rose
賣完這批鈴鐺
我的債就應該還清了
We will pay off the debt after
these bells are sold out.
說真的，男人真的蠻好用的
You know,sometimes,Man is useful.
能挑能扛，帶孩子煮飯
Man could do some heavy word,
cook,take care of child.
捏腳按摩樣樣精通
Even massage!
想生孩子的話
If you wanna have a baby,
可以選一個超猛超帥的來配一配
You could try to find handsome man.
不過千萬不要動真情
However,do not fall in love.
因為在天女國
男人都是女人的奴隸
Because man is always a slave in Kingdom of Amazons.
皇宮裡一個男人都沒有
There is no man in the Palace.
因為女皇恨男人
Because the Queen hate man.
大家好，我春十三少
今天首次獨挑大樑
Hello.I am Spring.First time for me.
別說我把好東西藏起來不給你們看
Don't think I am hiding something.
今天我一來
就拿出了我們的鎮店之寶
Today,I will show you the best we have.
也就是小弟精心調教的極品
This is a perfect product.
這位，就是只有十八歲的「硬梆梆」
This is "Ying BangBang",who is only 18.
大家過來看…
Come over and look!
你看你看，細皮嫩肉的
See,soft skin.
摸起來還很有彈性呢
是不是很想摸？
Nice Body,
You wanna touch him,right?
硬梆梆，轉個圈給大家看看
"Ying BangBang",turn around!
他洗衣燒飯，能挑能扛，任勞任怨
He could do anything,laundry,cook,etc.
保證不讓你失望
He will not disappointed you.
現在正好夏季大減價
And now,we have a special price.
只賣兩個金幣而已
Only two gold coins!
我出三個金幣
I will pay for 3!!
這生意當然是價高者得
Obviously,the one who pay the most will win.
謝謝你，老闆！
Thank you,Boss.
你幹嘛？
What are you doing?
不要…我不要
No,I don't want it.
你什麼意思？難道我的錢是假的？
What?You think these are fake coin?
這位老闆，先別生氣，我來擺平他
Hi,Sir,Don't be mad,I will take care of it.
你活得不耐煩啦？
What the hell,you wanna die?
不是啊
No.
你看她臉上，有顆那麼大的痣
Look,there is a big naevus on her face.
上面還有根毛，我頂不順啊
There is even a hair on it.I don't like it.
你想挑客是吧
挑個皇后給你好不好？
You are so picky
Wanna have a queen?
你讓我死吧！
Let me go to hell!
等一等，那麼傻幹嘛？
Wait,don't be stupid?
你看看我
Take a look at me.
我漂不漂亮？
Am I pretty?
漂亮
Yes
那她漂不漂亮？
How about her?
漂亮
She is pretty too.
你放過我吧，你要交差很容易
Let me go,it's easier for you to finish your job.
你隨便選個鈴鐺就行了
Ok,just take a bell.
我給你一千個金幣
I will give you 1000 gold coins.
站住！站住！
Stop!Don't run.
石板呢？
Where is the flag stone?
臥虎大哥，你叫我從皇宮偷的石板…
Mr.Hiding Tiger,the one you asked me to steal
from the palace.
在這裡
Right here.
按原定計劃，三天後見
Stay with original plan.See you in 3 days.
兩生花開，帝皇星現
Star of King appears.
乾坤倒轉，天下大亂
The world is messing around.
兩生花開，帝皇星現
Star of King appears.
乾坤倒轉，天下大亂
The world is messing around.
封鎖現場，圍捕亂黨！
Block and close the scene,go get the enemy!
我的鈴鐺全跑了，快追！
God,all of my bells runs away,go get them!
有沒有看到我的鈴鐺？
Did you say my bells?
有，剛剛抓了兩個
Yes,I catch two of them.
把鈴鐺還給我！
Give them back to me!
你不要跑！
Don't run!
你搞什麼？這麼下流
What are doing?You are so dirty.
搶了人家鈴鐺還要打人？
What,you have my bells,and you wannt hit me?
你知不知道你很煩？
Don't you konw you are so annoying?
你把鈴鐺還給我，我就不煩了
I will stay away if you give the bells back to me.
我說我沒有見過，不要逼我出手
Don't make me kick your ass,
I said I didn't see those bells.
你想動手是嗎？我才不怕你呢！
You wanna fight?Come on!
她是誰？
Who is she?
不關你的事
Nothing to do with you.
那個人是你抓的？
Did you get him?
他的傷痕不像是你做的
It doesn't seems that you did it
用不著你管，總之我把犯人抓回來
完成任務不就行了
Whatever,anyway,I got him,and my job is done.
怎麼樣？
How is it?
就抓回來兩個，其他都給跑了
Only got two,the others are gone.
就抓回這麼兩個瘦排骨？
Just these two skinny ones?
總比沒有好啊
It's better than nothing.
把他們帶回去煮湯啦！
Bring them back and make the soup!
你就是春十三少嗎？
Are you Spring?
幹嘛？知道錯來道歉了？
What,you wanna apologize?
你把我的生意全都破壞了
You ruin my business.
快把我的鈴鐺抓回來！
Give all my bells back!
原來是依多波曼大將軍
Oh,you are General Ermando.
今天怎麼這麼有空啊？
Why you are so available today?
你還記得我嗎？
Do you remember me?
記得！
Yes!
當然記得了，不過…
Of course.But,Uh...
我最近手頭不太方便
I am kinda of short on Money lately.
行了
I see.
你幫我找個人
Can you go to look for a man for me?
這筆賬，一筆勾銷
If you find him,everything is cancel off.
有這種好事？
Really?
那你要我找什麼人？
Whom do you want me to look for?
是一個男人
A man.
一個對我很重要的男人
Who is very important to me.
他很帥吧？
Is he very handsome?
他實在很特別，一點都不普通
He is very special,and not common at all.
跟大將軍真是天生一對
You guys are very similiar.
那麼請問他貴姓？
What's his name?
他在城外演戲的
He is acting outside of the town.
那種戲犯法的
However,that is illegal.
那怎麼找？
So,what should I do?
他很特別，有一種男人味
He is special,a special man.
什麼男人味？
What kinda man?
就是一種…
A kind of...
不像現在男人…
He is not like the men nowadays...
的男人
That kinda man.
那有沒有具體一點的記號？
Any further details?
有！
Yes!
他一看到美女，他的耳朵…
Whenever he see a pretty women.He is ear...
就砰一下，紅卜卜的
His ear will get red right away.
大人你的樣子…很陶醉…
Hey General,wake up.
就這樣吧
Ok,well.
你一定要幫我把他找回來，知道嗎？
You must find him,ok?
我的鈴鐺…
My bells...
暫時充公
The bells are confiscated for now.
如果你給我找到那個人
If you find that man.
我全部都還給你
I will give everything back to you.
十三少，快來救我，快來贖我…
Spring,Help me.Bail me out...
今天我失去的…
Whatever I lost today...
明天我一定要回來！
I will get everything back tomorrow!
紅鷲
Red Eagle
你找暴狼族的人幫忙抓他？
Did you ask people from "Wild Wolf" to get him?
沒錯
Yes.
你身為皇宮的玄機使
As an officer in the Palace.
絕對不可以跟野蠻的獸族人合作
Don't not cooperate with people from "Wild Wolf".
大祭司，這有什麼關係？
Why is that?
你交給我的任務，我都已經完成了
I did what you told me.
可是你不能不擇手段
But not in a right way.
你憑什麼教訓我？沒大沒小
How dare you say that to me?You need to respect.
沒大沒小的人是你！
You are the one with no respect!
你是玄機使，你就要聽我的命令！
You XuanJi Officer,you have to listen to me!
在這裡我只聽女人命令
I only listen to women here.
不會聽男人的
Not man.
再說…
And...
你也不算是一個真正的男人
You are not a real man.
走開
Get out of here.
大祭師，你放過她吧
Please,let her go.
從現在開始，你已經不是玄機使
From now on,you are not XuanJi Officer anymore.
女皇陛下
Your majesty.
你身為皇宮禁軍統領
As the person who is in charge of security team.
皇宮密室有人偷東西
Someone stole something from the
Secret room in our Palace.
當時，你為什麼不在現場指揮抓賊？
At that time,why didni't you do anything?
女皇陛下
Your majesty!
當時我在城門外監督修建城牆
I am watch those who are fixing the wall at that time.
而且，女皇曾經下令
And,You ever said:
皇宮密室是禁地
The secret room is forbidden.
更何況，現在只不過是
不見了一塊石頭嘛
And,we only lose a flagstone.
閉嘴！
Shut up!
我知道你當時去妓院嫖男人了
I know you are fucking with someone at that time.
賜你死刑！
And you will get a death penalty!
女皇陛下…
Your Majesty...
拉出去，殺！
Get him out,kill him!
是！
Yes!
最討厭看到雙雙對對的
I hate those matched couple.
女皇真的是越來越變態
The Queen is getting crazy.
兩生花開，帝皇星現
The star of King appear,
乾坤倒轉，天下大亂
The world is messing around.
怎麼樣，他們誰是帝皇星？
How is it?Who is the Star of King.
兩個都不是
Both of them are not.
殺！
Kill him!
前皇族的族譜上，只剩下這一個了
There is only one left on the family tree.
那麼他一定就是我們要找的帝皇星
So,he must be the Star of King.
我現在最擔心是那塊石板
會落入帝皇星的手上
I worried about that flagstone.
I don't want him to have it.
然後被他破解了石板之迷
找到那把神劍
If he decode the flagstone,and find the sword.
那就麻煩了
That will be a huge trouble.
雖然那塊石板
被臥虎藏龍的叛黨偷走了
Even the flagstone is stolen by
Croching tiger,hidden dragon group.
可是他們未必知道帝皇星在哪裡
However,they might know where is
The star of King.
臥虎藏龍不知道，可是那石板知道
They don't know,the flagstone knows.
它是有靈性的
它自己會找到真正的帝皇星
It has spiritualism
It could find the star by itself.
跟蹤那塊石板下落
就一定會找到帝皇星
Follow wherever the flagstone is.
You find the star.
找到又怎麼樣？
Even we find the star,so what?
他注定要坐你的位子
He is doomed to take your place.
你找死？
What,you wanna die?
你把我殺了吧！
Kill me place!
我怎麼捨得殺你呢？我還沒恨夠
How could I kill you?I am not that bad.
女皇，她是你妹妹啊
Your majesty,she is your sister!!
你心痛啊？
You are feeling the pain?
我…
I...
不好
Oh
你的傷口…         不許碰我！
-Your wound...
-Don't touch me!
永遠都不許碰我
Never,ever touch me!!!
你碰過的東西…
Whatever you have touched...
我都不要
I don't want tham.
姐姐，預言說
Sister,the predict said that
我們嫁給皇帝，就可以得到天下
If we are married with the King,We will get the world
你不可能為了愛情放棄這個世界
You cannot lose the world,only for the love.
我可以
But I can.
我有尉繚就夠了
I have Nei Liao
尉繚！
Nei Liao!
雅歌？
Ya Ge?
那麼她是…
So,she is...
你是雅婷？
You are Ya Ting?
雅婷，我永遠不會原諒你！
Ya Ting,I will never forgive you!
有人行刺皇上！
Someone try to assassinate the King!
從此以後
From now on.
我要全天下的男人…
I will make all men in the world...
忍辱偷生
Suffer and Torture
全都受我控制
All of them will be under my control.
立刻追查石板下落
Go to get any information about the flagstone,Now
飛鷹會帶你去找偷石板那個人
The Eagly will bring you to find the one
Who stole the flagstone.
還有，他被女兵們圍捕的時候
And,when he was besiedge by our soldier.
左手手臂受了刀傷
He has the cut would on his left arm.
找到馬上通知我
Tell me whenever you find him.
瞭解
Got it.
預備…
Prepare...
一、二、三，上！
1,2,3,Go!
不好意思，再來一次
Sorry,again.
你搞什麼嘛？
What are you doing?
不好意思，計算錯誤
Sorry,a mistake.
你沒事吧？
Are you ok?
臭小子！
You idiot!
你們今晚休想有飯吃！
Don't even think about the dinner tonight!
桃桃呢？    不知道
-Where is Peachy?
-I don't know.
都開場了，沒有女主角怎麼行？
We cannot start it without leading role!!
瓜子，去穿桃桃的衣服
Melon Seed.Go get the cloth of Peachy,and try it on.
黑木爺，這次一定沒問題
Master Blackwood.We would have no problem this time.
再來一次
Again
在很久很久以前，有一對雙胞胎仙女
Once Upon a time.There are a fairy twins
天神很希望把她們一起娶了做老婆
The god want to marry them all.
可是，妹妹卻好像有點煩惱…
However.the younger sister seems to have a trouble...
剛好來得及！    你跑哪去了？
-Just on time!
-Where are you?
黑木爺到處找你
Master Blackwood is looking for you everywhere.
你的手…
Your hand...
沒什麼，小意思
Don't worry.not a big deal.
我跟臥虎藏龍做大事，賺大錢
I have a business with Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon.
I will make big money.
臥虎藏龍？
Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon?
就是被人通緝的臥虎藏龍？
The one who is the most wanted now?
他很了不起啊！
He is super!
三天之後，我去跳虎崖
把這塊東西交給他
I wil give this to him at Tiger Jump Cliff
in 3 days.
然後我就不會再回來了
After the,I would never return.
這是…不要碰它！很值錢…
This is...Don't touch it!!It worth a lot of money.
臭小子！你跑哪去，這麼晚才回來？
You stupid!Where are you,you are late.
什麼東西值錢？    出場了…
-What are you guys talking about?
-Get on the stage.
出場了… 快換衣服！
Go,go to change your cloth!
預備… 一、二、三…
Prepare!1,2,3!
他一看到美女，他的耳朵…
Whenever he see a pretty women,His Ear...
就砰一下，紅卜卜的
His ear will get red all of a sudden.
我漂不漂亮？
Am I Pretty?
漂亮
Yes,you are.
幹什麼？
What?
黑木爺，你幫我卜一課吧
Master Blackwood.Give me a augury.
你都快要出場了，還占卜？
You are ready for the play.An Augury!?
拜託，很重要
Please,it is very important.
什麼事那麼重要？
What is so important?
姻緣
Marriage.
拿去自己看
Ok,here,take it and have a look.
白馬
White Horse.
人獸不能配，這邊！
Human and beast don't match each other.This side!
黑木爺，好靈啊！
Master Blackwood,you are good!
靈了是嗎？    靈！
See,I told you!
開心了嗎？    開心！
-Are you happy now?
-Happy!
開心就好好做事，走    好
-You could work well if you are happy.
-Good luck.
我漂不漂亮？
Am I pretty?
漂亮
Pretty.
認真一點
Be serioius.
漂亮
You are pretty.
用點感情！
Say it with some emotion!
真的漂亮！
You are so pretty!
紅卜卜的，一定是你
Red like a apply.Gotta be you.
走！
Go!
繼續…
Continue...
維維，你不是說只喜歡我一個嗎？
Weiwei,Don't you every say that you only like me?
可惡！
Damn!
你是老大？那麼你是…
Are you the head?Or,you are...
姐姐…不關我的事啊！
Sister...It has nothing do to with me!
其實是她用魔法…
It is actually her magic...
不聽，不聽…
I won't listen,no listening...
我恨死你了！
I hate you!
你真的搞錯了
I think you made a mistake.
我不要
I don't want it.
你碰過的東西，我都不要
I don't want have whatever he touched.
炭頭！
Charcoal Head!
讓我留在你身邊吧
Let me stay with you.
所有男人都不可以接近我
No man could get close to me.
既然你這麼恨男人…
Since you hate man so much.
好！我就切！
Well!I will do it
全都給我捉起來！
Arrest them all!
誰讓你們演這種鬧劇？
Who told you to play lsuch a joke?
什麼事…什麼事？
What's up...What's going on?
全都給我帶走！
Take them all!
是！
Yes!
快跑！兒子！
Run!My son!
站住！別跑！
Don't move!Stop!
對不起…
Sorry...
出來！
Get out!
快出來！
Get out as soon as possible!
謝謝
Thank you.
我還以為你那麼快找到石板
I thought you found the flagstone already.
吃餅吧
Have a cake.
把石板交出來
Turn in the flatstone.
我看你是個人材
I consider you as a talented man.
當我拿到了神劍之後
我可以封你做大祭司
I want you to be "JISI" after I got the Sword.
到時候，我們可以一起去打江山
After than,let's build our kindom together.
我們根本就不同路
We are not on the same boat.
好吧，那你就當你的忠心僕人吧
Well,just keep being a royal slave.
這是什麼？
What is this?
是昨天桃桃偷偷交給我的
Peach gave it to me yesterday secretly.
他叫我明天一起交還給那個…
He ask me to give this to that...
臥虎藏龍
Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon.
然後跟著他一起賺大錢
I will make some money with him after then.
寶石啊！
What a diamond!
發財了
We will get rich.
這是地圖
This is the map.
這不是多依河嗎？
Is this River Duo yi?
我知道了，這是藏寶地圖
I see,this is the mapy for treasure.
寶石的位置就是寶藏
The position of the dimond is where the treasure is at.
我知道…那座…
Oh,I know...
柴頭還沒回來？多烤條魚給他吃
Block head is not back yet,grill some fish for him.
炭頭呢？
Where is charcoal head?
炭頭東西呢？
Where is his stuff?
咕咕，你說
Googoo,tell me.
他們拿著石板，去找臥虎藏龍
They have the flagstone,and went to look for
Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon.
說去尋寶
They said they are looking for some treasure
尋寶？尋什麼寶？
Treasure?What treasure?
聽說臥虎藏龍是一個很威武的人
I heard about Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon
is a strong,handsome man.
貼好了，小意思嘛
Ok,done.piece of cake.
不對吧
No,it's not right.
再試試
Try again.
炭頭
Charcoal head.
天氣不錯
What a nice day
我就是臥虎藏龍
I am Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon.
女人？
Women?
白馬？
White Horse?
我英俊瀟灑
騎匹白馬有什麼大驚小怪？
I am handsome,and ride on a white horse.
You don't have to fuss.
你去看我們演過戲
Have you ever watch our play?
我們出來混的
當然什麼事都要小心點
I have to be careful of anything
since I make a living everywhere.
這種小功夫怎麼少得了
You have to have this kinda skill.
是呀…
Yes,you are right.
把藏寶圖給我
Show me the map.
桃桃呢？怎麼沒看見他？
Where is Peachy,I did see her.
我剛剛叫他找第二個寶藏
他現在發達了
I just asked him to go for the 2nd treasure.
He will get rich this time.
他發達啦
Yes he will.
大哥，我好想跟著你
Master,I want to work with you and follow you.
我一向獨來獨往
I usually come and go alone.
大哥，你拼不出來的
It's too hard for you.
我是做大事的人
I am someone who would do something big.
這種雞毛蒜皮的事
當然讓手下去做
So,you should let us do such piece of cake.
我們就是你手下啦
We are your understrapper.
這種粗重的事讓我們來做
Let us do these kinda stuff.
你帶我們一起去
Bring us with you.
你們倆個要脅我是不是？
Are you forcing me?
我收你們做手下，你們負責帶路
Ok,I will accept you guys.You need to lead me the way.
你又是誰？
Who are you?
臥虎藏龍
Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon.
你是臥虎藏龍，那他又是誰？
You are Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon
And,who is him?
臥虎藏龍那麼能打
He is a good fighter.
誰打贏了不就是誰
Who win,who would be the real one.
你來得剛好
Well,you just come on the right time.
其實我們倆個都是臥虎藏龍
Actually,both of us are Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon
我臥虎，她藏龍
I am Crouching Tiger.She is Hidden Dragon
我們是兩姐妹
We are sisters.
你不也是為了寶藏嗎？不如我們合作
You are looking for the treasure,too,aren't you?
How about,working together.
免得一拍兩瞪眼
This could avoid any conflict.
我們是好姐妹！
We are good sisters!
好好的幹嘛粘著鬍子？
Why do you have that mustache on?
是這樣子，現在流行
Well,it is popular to have a mustache now.
你要不要？撕一半給你怎樣？
You like it,I can give you half piece of my mustache?
我們走
Let's go.
找到寶藏後，我們也有份嗎？
Are we going to get some of the treasure
after we find them?
分你們一成
10%
有沒有搞錯啊？這麼大方
What?That is good.
戴起來！
Get this on!
我們說做你的手下
I said I will work for you.
沒說要做你的鈴鐺
But I have see I will sell the bells for you,too.
對，我們不做鈴鐺那玩意
Yes,we don't do nothing about bells.
所以說你們沒學問
So,you are stupid.
男人走在街上是犯法的
Man walking in the street is illlegal
這叫障眼法
This is called camouflage
走
Let's go.
先說好，這件事是我先發現
I have to make it clear.
I am the first one to discover this.
假如找到寶藏以後，我要分大的
I need something more than 10% after we find them.
好
No proglem.
我七你三
70% for me,30% for you.
好
Deal!
我八你二才對
You know what,it should be 80-20
好
Well,ok.
這麼大方？
Like that?
你別坑我，我很聰明的
Don't play with me.I am not stupid.
我好想把他們賣掉做鈴鐺
I really want to sell them to make the bells.
對對對…我忘記大家都是同行
Right,right,we are doing the same business.
可是酷點那個…我已經有客人訂了
But,that cool one...My client have reserved.
沒問題…
No problem.
你肚子餓不餓？
Are you hungry?
你們兩個    是
-Hey,you two.
-Yes,Sir.
抓隻兔子給我做晚餐
Go get a rabbit for our dinner.
好！
Yes,Sir!
這邊
There.
那邊
That side.
我說在那邊嘛    那裡也有！
-I said this side.
-There is one there,too!
那邊
That side.
你沒事吧？
Are you ok?
痛不痛？
How is it?
兩位大爺，可不可以不吃它？
My master,Do we have to eat it?
它受了傷，而且樣子可愛
It is wounded,and it is so cute.
既然它那麼可憐
那我們就不吃它了
Ok,we won't eat it since it is cute.
那吃你好了！
So,you will be our dinner!
一點用都沒有
放了它我們晚上吃什麼？
Idiot,what do we have if you let it go?
說打呢，你還有一套
Talking about fighting,you are good.
至於男人，你哪裡有我經驗豐富
Talking about being a man,I am a Pro.
我還以為你很專業呢
I thought you are so professional
我們賣鈴鐺的
怎麼可以付出真感情？
We could not bring out our real heart since
we sells bells.
你能這麼說就對了
Yeah,you are right.
不就是男人嘛，說說話沒有關係
Come on,it doesn't matter.
可是，我看你對那塊木炭…
But,I think you have a crush on that Charcoal Head.
好像不大對勁…
It is not normal.
你是不是對他動了真情？
Are you falling in love?
神經病
Stupid.
這有什麼好害羞的？
我們都是女人嘛，喜歡就說
Don't be shy?
We are women,we could talk about this kinda stuff.
我對那木炭…一點興趣都沒有
I am interested in Charoal head at all.
好，你不要，我要了
Ok,if you don't want him.I will take him.
隨便
Whatever.
那我就不客氣了
Ok,I will do it.
你興奮一點，大聲一點
You  better shout,and let everyone know.
其實…臥虎他…
Actually,Crouching Tiger...He,uh...
臥虎大爺，床我已經鋪好了
Mr.Crouching Tiger,I have made the bed for you.
還有什麼吩咐？我什麼都行的
Anything else I can do?
那你最拿手的是什麼？
What are you good at?
鴛鴦嬉水
We could shower together.
還有呢？
Whatelse?
我這兩片烈火紅唇
I have two sexy lips.
還有…
And...
夠了…
Enough.
還好今天吃得不多
God,I am lucky that I didn't eat so much today.
不用了，你走吧
Ok,you could go now.
既然來了，你就讓我幫你擦個背吧
Come one,let me wash your back for you.
不用了啦
No.
我擦背超棒的
I could make you fell very comforble.
來嘛，試試看
Come one,just try.
我說不用了！
I said no!
最討厭人家自己送上門的
I hate when girl does this.
龍弟，你還生我氣？
Are you mad at me?
別那麼小器嘛
Come on.
臥虎哥，男人會讓我生氣？
Tiger,man could make me angry
你知不知道我在想什麼？
我在想寶藏
You know what I am thinking aobut now?
I am thinking about the Treasure.
錢呢！
How about money!
我們準備好了
Money is enough.
過來
Come over here.
你幹什麼？你以為自己是什麼？
What are you doing?Who do you think you are?
戴起來！木頭一樣
Wear it!You are like a woodhead.
年輕人，不要難過
Young guy,take it easy.
女人就是這樣，口是心非
Woman is always janus-faced.
餅來了，趁熱吃
Cake is coming,have some.
謝謝
Thank you.
吃餅吧
Have some cake.
我最討厭吃餅
I hate eating this.
這又何必呢？
Why?
不就是吃的嘛，又沒有得罪你
Just a cake.
對不對？
Right?
兩位美女
Two pretty girls.
我叫「傾國傾城」
不介意我坐下吧？
I am Miss Pretty.
Do you mind if sit here?
介意啊
Yes I mind.
介意我也得坐下
I will sit here anyway.
這位大娘，你蠻時髦的
Hey,you are pretty fashionable.
你那兩撇鬍子真是超性感
Especially your two piece of mustache.
這位美女真識貨，我老實告訴你吧
En,you got good taste.Let me tell you.
我剛剛在隔壁那家店做的
I make this from the shop over there.
絕對是真發，不是「行貨」
It's a actual hair.It's not fake.
這兩個當當看起來很嬌媚呀
It looks sexy.
對了，你們出不出讓？
You wanna sell it?
不如賣給我呀
Sell it to me.
我們不…    誰叫你說話？
No,who let you speak?
我們不賣
No.we don't sell
大娘，你年紀都這麼大了
How old are you.
這兩個當當你玩不動的
You cannot have these.
我告訴你們兩個
Let me tell you.
我是女皇的密使，帶著女皇的密令
I am The Queen's emissary.
專誠帶他們倆個回皇宮的
I need to bring them back to the palace.
女皇密使？證明呢？
Emissary?Prove it?
看仔細了，別貶眼睛
Look.
拿塊餅出來就說是女皇密使是吧？
The cake is the proof?
你有是吧？我還有呢
I have one,too.
你是誰？
Who are you?
臥虎藏龍！
Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon!
又是臥虎藏龍？
Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon again?
假的！
Fake one!
不好意思，多有冒犯
Sorry about this.
這杯酒，算我向你陪罪
This is for the apology.
算啦…
That's ok.
你剛才說那兩個混小子
其中一個是帝皇星？
You said one of those young guys is the Star of King?
那豈不是將來的皇帝？
That mean,he would be the next King?
不錯，根據預言…
Yes,according to the Predict...
這塊石板就可以引帝皇星出現
This flagstone will bring out the Star of the King.
找到鬼城，拿回神劍，推翻女魔王
Find the Ghost City,get the sword,and kill the Monster.
我們男人就不再受女魔王的壓迫
So,we don't have to suffer anymore.
我的責任就是要保護帝皇星
拿回神劍
Our responsibility is to protect our King
And,get the sword back.
你好偉大！
You are so great!
這皇帝你做定了，不用擔心
Don't worry,you will be the King for sure.
不一定呀
Not really.
你們兩個幹嘛討論得那麼興奮？
Then,why you guys are so excited?
說來說去，也不知真的假的
It's not even true.
而且要推翻女魔王
你們兩個能打嗎？
Are you two strong enough to kill the Queen?
算了
Forget about it.
趕快收拾東西，跟我回劇團
Wrap it up,and leave.
起碼下半輩子安安穩穩
I want it to be nice in the rest of our lives.
來…收拾東西
Come one,wrap it up.
黑木爺
Master Blackwood.
黑木爺，黑木爺…
Master Blackwood,Master Blackwood...
少廢話！我不跟你說了
Shut up.I have nothing to say to you.
黑木爺…
Master Blackwood.
你冷靜一點
心平氣和聽我說好不好？
Come down and listen to me,ok?
兩位，可不可以借個火？
Hey,can I borrow the lighter?
我不抽煙
I don't smoke.
我漂不漂亮？
Am I pretty?
你們兩個還不趕快收拾東西？
Hurry up and let's go home?
差點被那兩個傢伙攪和了
They almost ruin everything.
你們又不是臥虎藏龍
You are not Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon.
你不是要寶藏嗎？
跟誰有什麼關係？
Are you looking for the treasure?
Anything to do with someone?
就是嘛，你跟他們又凶又笨
See,they are bad and stupid.
誰好誰壞都不知道
They cannot even recognize who is bad or nice.
走了…
Let's go.
這樣子丟下黑木爺，不太好吧？
We cannot just leave Master Blackwood there alone.
你看他們現在多好
They are doing good there.
等我做了皇帝，黑木爺就不用愁了
Master Blackwood would be happy after I become the King.
你又可以跟夢中情人在一起了
And you could stay with your dream man.
你這東西真有用
This is good.
銷魂香嘛
所有賣鈴鐺的都會有這東西
Everyone who sell bells,has it.
你沒有嗎？
You don't have it?
給你
Here you go.
可以走了
Ready to go.
那快點
Hurry up.
快點啊
Come on,hurry up.
炭頭，如果我做了皇帝…
Charcoal,if I am the King.
我們男人就不用再做奴隸了
We will not be the slaves anymore.
不過，說不定你才是皇帝呢
Maybe,you will be the King.
我有信心一定是你
I am confident that you will be the one.
我幫你吧
I will help you.
皇室寶藏…應該有很多錢
There should be a lot of money there.
靠那麼近幹嘛，我跟你很熟？
Don't get close to me,Do I know you?
你不要誤會我，我不是來巴結你的
Don't misunderstand.
你以為我很想做皇后？
You think I want to be the Queen?
我才不稀罕，那麼累
I don't like it.
好肉麻
So sick.
明明是想做想得想死了，還不承認
You don't say it,but I know you want it so much.
我是一個很有上進心的人
I am working hard.
柴頭最瞭解我了
Charcoal knows me.
最恨人家那麼主動
I hate this.
你不知道摸女人是犯法的嗎？
Don't you touching women is illegal?
砍掉你的手！
Chop your hand!
快要到鬼城了
We are getting close to Ghost City.
還說是鬼城，都沒有鬼
There is no ghost here.
你不就是鬼嗎？
You are one?
我是個艷鬼嘛
I am a sexy Ghost
走啊，快走
Go,hurry up.
不要怕啊，我保護你
Don't be afraid.I will bless you.
爬樹
Climb the trees.
這是什麼鬼地方，怎麼這麼恐怖
What the hell is this,so scary.
說了是鬼城嘛
It is Ghost City,I told you.
鬼？我最怕就是鬼了！
What,I am scared.
你小聲點
這麼大聲會把鬼引出來呀
Be Quiet.
那你抓緊我啊！
Hold me tight.
別那麼用力呀！
Too much.
把石板給我
Give me the flagstone.
紅鷲！
Red Vulture!
小心呀！
Watch out!
你為什麼要救我？
Why did you save me?
雖然我們不同路
Even we are not on the same boat.
我們還是從小一起長大的好姐妹
We are still good sisters.
可是你根本不知道我心裡在想什麼
But,you don't even know what I am thinking.
我當然知道
做皇帝真的對你那麼重要嗎？
Of course I know.
Being a King is that important to you?
今生今世
In my whole life.
做不成皇帝
If I cannot be the King.
我死都不甘心
I will die sadly.
抓緊，不要放手
Hold it tight.
紅鷲！
Red Vulture!
我不想這麼年輕就死
I cannot die young.
放心吧，我們不會死的
Don't worry.We will not die.
如果我死呢？
If I die?
你記住一定要抓住我的手啊
Remember to hold my hand.
我怕一個人…
I am afraid of one man.
原來你們是人？
You are humans?
沒錯！我們就是…
Yes...
遁地人
The man of underground.
我是帕路帕
I am PaluPa
我是卡古卡
I am Kaguka
你笑我笑
You smile.
你哭我哭
You cry.
你凶我凶
You bad.
你殺我殺
You kill
你們抱抱，我們抱抱
Hug me,haha.
笑…
Laughing.
我們要笑
I wanna laugh.
笑啊…
Haha.
你認真一點嘛
Be serious.
你一點用都沒有！
You are useless!
也不抓緊人家
You should hold me tight.
是你呀
It's you.
平時叫你多吃點東西嘛
也不聽人家話
I told you eat more,but you never listen to me.
討厭
Hate you.
閉嘴！閉嘴！
Shut up.
耍我？
You are playing with me?
跟我去找炭頭
Come one,let's go to look for Charcoal Head.
我們遁地族的祖先
本來生活在北方的草原
We are teh ancience of Underground man.
We are originaly from Northern Grassland.
在那裡我們生活得自由自在
We have a nice life there.
我們想笑就笑
We could laugh whenver we want.
我們想哭就哭
Cry whenever we want.
可是我們熱愛工作
我們白天拚命做
We love working,and we are hard working.
晚上拚命玩
Have fun at night.
可是那個女皇看不慣我們那麼開心
However,the Queen don't like these.
她不准我們有愛情
We are not allowed to love.
所以，我們只好躲在這個山洞裡面
So,we have to hide in this cavity.
繼續過我們的生活
To continue our life.
可是你看看，躲呀躲的…
You could see,we are hiding everywhere.
我們統統都變得神神鬼鬼
We became Ghosts.
瘋瘋癲癲…還很怕見到陽光呢
Get crazy,and we cannot see the sunshine.
我們要報仇…
We want to revenge.
帕路帕大哥，冷靜點！冷靜點！
PaluPa,calm down.
報仇！報仇…
Revenge,revenge.
這些東西是不是你的？
Are those yours?
是，謝謝
Yes,thanks.
還有這個呢？
How about this?
這是什麼？很好看
What is this?It looks good.
不要碰！
Dont' touch it.
炭頭
Charcoal.
炭頭…
Charcoal...
柴頭
Blockhead.
這裡好大的霧啊，好恐怖啊
It's too foggy here.
等霧散了我們再走吧
Let's go after the fog is gone.
炭頭！
Charcoal.
靠著石頭，好像安全一點
It is safe befhind the rock.
柴頭…
Blockhead
是我們啊
It's us.
是你們？
You?
我還以為你被妖怪吃了
I thought you are gone.
不是妖怪，是遁地族的人
They are not ghost but underground man.
他們好好玩呀
The are so funny.
你們幹嘛手牽手？
Why you are hand in hand?
你們也抱得很緊呀
And hold each other this tight?
我跟你很熟啊？
I know you well?
幹嘛？我現在讓你抱是便宜你了
What,you are taking advantage of me if you hug me.
怎麼這裡霧這麼大
這裡是什麼地方？
What is this place,too foggy here.
有道門    對呀
There is a door.
應該是這裡了，千軍塚的入口
Here,the entrance.
太好了…找到了！找到了！
Nice,I found it.
怎麼打開？
How to open it?
是這裡了
Right here.
要不要用塊石板？
Do we need that flagstone?
這什麼鬼地方？
What is this damn place?
不要管了，走吧
Forget about it,let's go.
有好多武器啊
So many weapons here.
金銀財寶呢？
Where is the treasure?
不是說有把神劍嗎？
There should be a sword here?
這麼多把，哪一把才是呀？
There are many of them,which one is the real one?
剋星來了，快走啊！
He is coming,Let's go!
快跑！快跑！
Hurry Up,run!
每次看到這個傢伙就倒霉
We have bad luch everytime when we see him.
怎麼搞的？只有一池水四面牆…
What,only a pool,and walls.
什麼都沒有
Nothing else.
很好玩
Interesting.
你們看
Look.
是我！
That's me!
怎麼會是我以前的事？
Why is was my past?
耍騙術！
It's cheat!
給錢啊！
Give me money
你耍騙術！
You just cheat!
自己人也騙？
Cheat your mates?
什麼！什麼…
What!what...
騙自己人？
Cheat mates?
什麼？
What?
有把劍
There is a sword.
對！
Yes!
真的有把劍啊！
There is a sword!
那你就是皇帝，我就是皇后
Then you are the king,I'm the queen.
我們就要發財了？
We'll be rich.
做人謙虛點好
Be a nice man.
看來你不像一個普通的戰士
You looks don't like a normal fighter.
我是正陽族的臥虎藏龍
I'm Zheng Yang Tribe's warrior.
在下是前朝的護國將軍，衛城
I'm the past dynasty's general.
押錯注了
Bet wrong
我有說過自己是皇帝嗎？
Did I said I'm the king?
是你說的，是你自己想當皇后
You said,you want to be the queen.
幹嘛？做不成皇帝拿我出氣？
Vent your anger to me?
還好沒把身體押下去
It's lucky I didn't bet my body
不然我就虧大了！
then I lost so much!
你再說一次
You say it again.
再說一次就再說一次
I don't care.
什麼？   柴頭，算了吧
What?Blockhead,forget about it.
走開
Go away.
你是碰巧的，你不會是帝皇星的
Just was lucky,you are not The Star of the King.
快把劍丟掉啊
Drop the sword.
我沒想過要拿這把劍
I never thought take this sword.
柴頭，我真的不是故意的
Blockhead,that's not my purpose.
快點放回去！
Put it back!
藍翎
Blue.
立刻追查石板下落
Find where is Armour right now.
找到帝皇星就馬上通知我
Let me know if you find The Star of the King.
瞭解
Roger.
原來你是奸細
You are the spy.
別讓她跑了！
Don't let her escape!
你沒事吧？
Are you all right?
為什麼…
Why...
你快點放了炭頭！
Release Charcoal Head now!
你為你的國家，我也為我的國家
You do for your country,and me for my country.
你一直都是在欺騙我
You cheat me all the time.
對不起…
I'm sorry...
你要這把劍是嗎？我不要…
Did you want this sword?I don't want it...
我給你！
I give it to you!
帝皇星出現，花都有救了
The Star of the King appears,Huadu got chance.
以後的事情就交給你了
Everything is yours now.
痛死我了    炭頭！
Hurt.
-Charcoal Head!
我不是故意的，我控制不了…
It's not my purpose,I can't control myself...
你們走吧
You go first.
走啊…
Go...
走啊！
GO!
我不要做皇帝！
I don't wanna be king!
皇帝？胡弄人！
King?
死要錢！
You only know money!
妹妹剛剛跟我說
Sister just told me.
真正的帝皇星已經得到了神劍
The Star of the King already got the Sword.
你放心，我已經有計劃
Take easy,I already have plan.
一定會抓到帝皇星和拿到那把神劍
We will get The Star of the King and the Sword.
要號令天下，要管治人
If you want conquest the world,order others.
就要果斷、無情
You must be cool and cold-blood
有這種性格才可以駕馭神劍
With that,you might be control the Sword.
別以為一個乳臭未乾的孩子
Never thought a kid
拿到把劍就可以對付我
can fight me with the Sword.
簡直是自掘墳墓
It's killing himself.
大祭司，對不起
Flamen,I'm sorry.
我不配做玄機使
I'm not good enough to be an emissary.
不用說了，你的雙眼已經告訴我
Stop sayying that,your eyes already told me.
任務失敗，是因為你動了情
You failed becouse you move your emotion.
我沒用
I'm useless.
你走吧
You go.
為什麼女皇對你那麼差
Why queen do that with you
你還留在她身邊？
You still stay together with her?
為自己喜歡的人付出
Pay for the one I like
是很自然的事
It's a naturally thing.
十三大爺，舒不舒服？
13th Master,do you feel good?
你把你的手拿開好不好？
Can you remove your hand from me?
我看到你就不舒服
I'm so sick with you.
真的？那我們玩醫生病人遊戲吧
Really?Then we could play doctor and patient game.
我最會當醫生了，咳兩下我聽聽
I'm so good to be a doctor,cough.
滾開你！
Get out!
什麼醫生病人，亂七八糟
What fuck the doctor and patient game.
他叫「踏浪而來」
His name is "Come with waves".
剛來了兩天，細皮嫩肉的
Come here two days ago.
叫人啊，好好招呼客人
Take good care of guest.
好一個「踏浪而來」
You have a cute name "Come with waves".
喝酒！
Drink!
換人啊！
Someone change!
大家都認識，何必那麼絕？
Why you doing that?We know each other?
那你就當什麼都沒發生過
把我當成那種…
You can thought nothing happened
And thought me like...
風流不羈，冷酷無情的浪子
Handsome man.
這樣才對
That's right.
我又沒錢，又不是皇帝
I'm poor,and not the king.
我是牛郎！
I'm cowboy!
喝酒吧
Just drink.
自甘墮落
Corrup yourself.
你好虛偽
You so hypocritical.
你當初也是想抓我當鈴鐺來賣嘛
You just want to sell me at first.
對啊…我就是死要錢
Yes...I just want money.
你不要錢？
You don't want money?
好啊！那我現在就抓你去賣給
那個胖將軍依多波曼
Ok!I'll catch you and sell to fat genera Edo Bowman.
說話算話
那我這一輩子就不用愁了
Nice,then I don't need to worry anything in my life.
現在就走啊！
Go now!
好啊，走就走啊！
Ok,just go!
走啊
Go.
這麼巧啊？
So coincident?
依多波曼大將軍
genera Edo Bowman.
你幫我找的男人，找到沒有？
Did you find the man?
再找不到，你的生意…充公！
If you still can't find him,your business...
我當然找到了
Of course I found him.
那人呢？
Where is him?
波曼
Bowman.
我在這裡，我們走吧
I'm here,let's go.
你幹什麼？
What are you doing?
不知道！
I don't know!
叫你走你就走呀！
Just go!
你還跑？
Still run away?
我就是你要找的夢中情人
I'm the one you want
帶我走吧，快把生意還給十三
take me go.
住嘴！
Shut up!
你好大的膽子！敢這樣跟我說話？
You so dare to talk me like that?
你以為隨便找個人
應付應付我就行了？
You thought I'm ok with anyone?
他不是你要找的人嗎？
Is he not the one you looking for?
不過…
But...
他也有一點點男人味
He like man too.
帶他回去！算是利息
Take him back!
你說帶就帶？
You can't order me.
他現在是我的
Now he is mine.
你愛上了鈴鐺？
You fall in love with Bells?
對啊…
Yes...
我就是愛上了鈴鐺，怎麼樣？
I'm fall in love with Bells.
鈴鐺老闆…愛上了鈴鐺…
Bells Boss love Bells...
很好笑嗎？不行啊？
Is that funny?Can't I?
你的生意不用做了，全部充公！
You can't do your business any more!
充死你好了，我還不想幹呢
You go to hell,and I just don't wanna do it anymore!
你現在跟我一樣窮了
Now you poor like me.
誰說的？我還有你
Who said?I still have you
我把你當成鈴鐺賣了…
I sell you as bells
不就有錢了
then I'll get money.
你捨得？
You will?
捨得
Yes.
你跑來幹嘛？
What are you doing here?
我想跟你說
我已經不是女帝的人了
I want talk to you.
Now I'm not Queen's man
還有，我希望你們通知炭頭
And,I hope you can notify Charcoal Head
即使他拿到神劍，也打不過女帝的
Even he got the Sword,he still can't fight with Queen.
叫他不要去送死
Tell him don't kill himself.
不管是真是假，趕快通知炭頭
I don't it was true or fake,just notify Charcoal Head
好不好？走！
Ok?Let's go!
你穿成這樣怎麼走？
How can we go with that dress?
我不是很漂亮嗎？
Am i pretty?
好，快點！
Ok.hurry up!
我早就知道她喜歡上帝皇星
I already know she like king.
帶他們去密室
Take them to secret chamber
我果然沒有猜錯
I'm right.
讓你動情的人就是帝皇星
The one who moves you is the king.
你想引他來？
You wanna let him come here?
大祭司，我求你放過他
Flamen,please let him go.
他根本不是女皇的對手
He absolutely can't fight with Queen.
我要的是那把神劍
I want that Sword.
原來你想做皇帝
Its you who wanna be king.
什麼皇帝？
King?
兩生花開，帝皇星現
The flowers op,The Star of the King appears
乾坤倒轉，天下大亂
the world would in chaos
兩生花…
The flowers...
我要它開就開，要它謝就謝
it open and fad as my mind.
姐姐，是我不好
Sister,Its my fault.
尉繚他根本就沒有背叛過你
Nei Liao never betray you
你原諒他吧
Forgive him.
原諒？
Forgive?
姐姐…
Sister...
對不起
I'm sorry.
我已經回不了頭了
I can't turn back
只有你最瞭解我
You are the only one who know me
你們兩個，一定要跟我一樣
You two,must same as me
有多愛…就有多恨！
Love as your hate!
各位部族的族長
Shaikh of each Tribe
帝皇星，已經得到神劍了
The Star of the King already got the Sword.
明天我們就可以殺進天女國
We can fight with Kingdom of Amazons tomorrow
打倒那個女魔王
And
你要我們跟那帝皇星去打仗？
You want us go war with The Star of the King?
可是你看看他的樣子…
But did you see what he looks like...
現在有得吃，有得住
只是受點女人氣
Now you get place to live,get food to eat.
Only have to endure women...
打仗，連命都會沒了
War will let you die.
命沒了還好一點
Even better than dead.
如果你們弄得像我這樣…
If you like me...
那可就慘了
That's too bad.
黑木爺，是不是你？
Master Blackwood,is that you?
你幫幫我…
Help me...
你的事情我已經全知道了
I already know everything about you.
我現在只想跟大家說幾句話
Now I just wanna have some words with you.
你是什麼人？
Who are you?
我不是人
I'm not human.
我是一個怪物
I'm a monster.
你在說什麼？
What are you talking about?
炭頭，你不要怕
Charcoal Head,don't be scared.
你們看到了
You see.
就是女魔王把我變成這個樣子
The Queen make me like this...
她為了要把男人變成女人
She want to trun man to woman.
所以把我抓去做實驗
So she experiment on me.
卻弄得我不男不女
Now I don't sure I'm a man or a woman.
如果你們再袖手旁觀不出手的話
If you just stay watch.
下一個變成怪物的…可能是你！
Next one who becouse monster...might be you!
是你！是你！也許會是你！
You!You!It might be you!
那我們就兵分兩路，上下夾攻
We should separate our army,and assail from two sides.
就算丟掉了自己的命，也要復國！
Even lost your life,you should restore your country!
炭頭！
Charcoal Head!
柴頭
Blockhead.
黑木爺
Master Blackwood.
對不起
I'm sorry.
先別說這個
Stop sayying that.
藍翎和十三少被女皇的人抓走了
Blue and Spring was cought by Queen.
炭頭，要做一個好皇帝…
Charcoal Head,to be a good king...
是不會只顧自己的
You can't just care yourself.
好！
Ok!
出來！
Come out!
我們既然敢來，就準備好要犧牲
We come here,already be ready for dead.
擺陣！
Arrange team!
列陣！
住手！
Stop!
依多波曼！
Edo Bowman!
這個人，我是不會放過他的！
This man,I won't let him go next time.
我想死你啦！
I miss you so much!
我以為這一輩子再也見不到你了
I thought I can't see you in my life.
不要哭，再哭就不美了
Don't cry.
你的耳朵還是這麼性感
Your ear always so sexy.
大庭廣眾，不要說得那麼肉麻
Before a big crowd,don't be sickeningly disgusting.
大將軍，我們到底還打不打？
General,should we fight or not?
不打…
No...
打！一定要打！
Fight!We must fight!
不過我們是聯手去打
However we should fight together.
只要推翻這個女魔王
If we overturn the Devil.
我們就可以過一些正常生活了
We'll have normal life.
大家不用擔心
Don't worry.
我們要推翻的是女魔王
不是女人
We overturn the Devil.Not woman.
將來的世界是男女平等
人人都有自由
The furture world have the equality of men and women.
Everyone have freedom.
有愛情，大家敢愛敢恨
With love.
好！
Ok!
好！我們就去剷除那個女魔王！
Ok!Let's clear Devil.
好！
Ok!
女魔王施法啦！跑啊！
Devil apply magic!run!
快點跑啊！
Run!
往有陽光的地方走！快走！
To the plave have sunshine!go!
我不走！我死都要跟你在一起！
I won't leave!I'm with you.
我不走，好不容易才跟你在一起
I won't leave,it's so hard to get together with you.
不管變成什麼我都不走！
I'll never leave!
皇上，過了這道門就是皇宮了
King,there is the palace
怎麼樣？    好痛
-Are you ok?
-So pain
藍翎！
Blue!
十三少！
Spring!
藍翎！
Blue!
十三少！
Spring!
藍翎！
Blue!
你幹什麼啊，藍翎？
what are you doing.Blue?
怎麼變成兩個瘋婆子？
Why just become two crazy bitch?
我不知道啊
I dont know...
你幹什麼呀？
what are you doing?
又來？
Again?
炭頭！不要！
Charcoal Head!Don't do that!
炭頭！
Charcoal Head!
挺住！炭頭！
Hold out!Charcoal Head!
不要…
No...
炭頭！
Charcoal Head!
喂，你沒事吧？
Hey.Are you all right?
藍翎，我是炭頭啊
Blue.I'm Charcoal Head.
藍翎
Blue.
不要鬧了，我們走吧
Don't be silly.Just let's go.
十三少，不要玩好不好？
Spring.Dont't waste your time ok?
藍翎，不要
Blue.no.
炭頭，你躺在地上幹嘛？
Charcoal Head,What are you doing with lie on the ground?
發生什麼事？
What's happen?
剛才你們兩個中了魔法，追殺我們
You two just wanna attack us.
你剛才像瘋子一樣的抓我
You just scratched at me like crazy.
什麼瘋子？我好好的幹嘛抓你？
What?Why i did that?
藍翎…
Blue...
慘了！
Shit!
好痛呀
So pain.
你沒事吧？
Are you all right?
不知道誰用麻袋套著我的頭來打我
Don't know who hit me with a gunny-bag cover my head.
你看，都把我掐紫了
You see?Already injured me!
是柴頭…
It's Blockhead...
你們兩個有沒有事啊？
Are you all right?
是你們兩個有沒有事才對
It should be are you all right.
不要再說了，我們趕快走吧
Don't waste time,let's go.
炭頭，快去把神劍拿回來
Charcoal Head,take that Sword back.
千萬不能讓女皇拿到神劍！
Never ever let Queen get the Sword.
炭頭！    炭頭…
-Charcoal Head!
-Charcoal Head...
柴頭，快去拿火救炭頭！
Blockhead.Go help Charcoal Head with fire!
你去拿神劍
You take the Sword.
我攔住女皇，快！
I stop Qeen,go!
炭頭！炭頭…
Charcoal Head!Charcoal Head...
你走開！
You go away!
炭頭，挺住，挺住
Charcoal Head.hold on.hold on.
好冷啊…
I feel so cold...
你沒事吧？
Are you ok?
挺住
Hold on...
我們可以的…
We can make it...
可以的
We can.
來！    我們可以的！
We can make it!
炭頭！不要！
Charcoal Head!No!
捨不得啊？
Reluctant to give up?
為了一個欺騙過你的人
你會放棄全世界？
Because a man who cheated you,
you'll give up the world?
連自己的命都不要？
Even give up your life?
炭頭，不要管我，砍下來！
Charcoal Head,just cut it off!
我不想死！
I don't wanna die!
又多了一個沒用的男人
One more usless guy
尉繚
Nei Liao
你教他把神劍拿起來
You teach him how to take the Sword.
學你那樣，閹了自己
Just like you,castrate yourself
也許…我就不會殺他
Mabye...I'll let him go.
她已經準備為你犧牲
She had ready to die for you.
你還不用神劍消滅女皇
Why don't you kill Queen with Sword?
女皇的怨恨會讓藍翎永遠痛苦
Queen will hate Bule forever.
對啊，要愛就要犧牲自己
You are right,you have to sacrifice if you wanna have love.
炭頭，不要把劍交給尉繚
Charcoal Head,don't give the Sword to Nei Liao
他是要拿劍做皇帝！
He need the Sword to be king.
你一直都在欺騙我？
You cheat me all the time?
再晚就沒機會了
Its the last chance.
你一直都在欺騙我！
You cheat me all the time!
閉上眼睛，我會幫你
Close your eye,I'll help you.
把劍拿起來！
Take that Sword!
藍翎，你有沒有事？
Blue,are you all right?
沒事
I'm ok.
只有這樣…
Only with that...
你才能變回原來的雅歌
How could you get back to the original YEGE.
別怕
Don't be scared.
我會一直在你身邊
I'm here.
不會離開你
I won't leave you.
永遠都不會
Never.
我沒騙過你…
I never cheat you...
一次都沒有
Even one time.
變什麼沒關係…
It's ok to change...
你先起來一下
Get up.
我受不了啦…
I can't handle it...
變…變什麼？
Change...what?
沒有了…
It's gone...
沒有了！
It's gone!
一定是炭頭打贏了…
Charcoal Head win...
我沒事了！
I'm ok!
那個炭頭真有一套
Charcoal Head so good.
放著皇帝不做，跑去享受人生
He don't wanna be a King.
留下一個國家讓我一個人管
And leave all the country to me.
對啊，真過癮
ya,so cool.
沒想到叉著雙手
就可以一輩子不用做事
I can't image I don't need to work in my life.
不如我們輪流吧
我一三五，你二四六
Hmm,Why don't we take turns?
You have 1,3,5 I have 2,4,6.
我才不幹呢
No way!
這麼種的活當然是你們男人去做
It was man's job.
不行
No way.
還是要趕快跟你做個皇子出來
分擔才行
It's better to have a son
He'll do some work.
好啊，什麼時候？
Ok,when?
不如現在
Now.
現在？    對啊
-Now?
-ya.
現在怎麼做？那麼多人
What should we do now?So many peple there.
沒關係，我是皇帝嘛
It's ok,I'm the king.
以後的事，就交給你們年青人了
I'll leave everything to you youngs.
漂亮吧？
Pretty?
是很漂亮，不過太冷了一點
Yes pretty,but a little cold.
就快到了
Almost there.
他們生了對雙胞胎！
They have twins now!
這怎麼行，我們也得做點事情
We should do somthing too.
做你的頭！
With what?
你為什麼不做皇帝
要和我在一起？
Why you don't wanna be a King?
You need stay together with me?
你知道
You know that
你不說，我會不記得
If you don't say,I'll never remember it.
喜歡你…
喜歡得連皇帝都沒時間做了
I like you so much,even have no time to be a king.
傻瓜，那我們走吧
Fool.Let's go.
好！
ok!